<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="pi_database" name="Halcyon Private Investigations LLC Database" type="4" icon="DLCServer" allowsDefaultBootModule="true">
    <ports>21,80,25,443</ports>
    <portsForCrack val="4"/>
    <portRemap>21=265,25=250,443=856</portRemap>
    <DatabaseDaemon Permissions="private" DataType="TextRecord" Foldername="database" Color="70,40,4" AdminEmailAccount="DBAdmin@jmail.com" AdminEmailHostID="jmail" Name="Halcyon Private Investigations LLC Case Database">
        <TextRecord>
            <Title>#4801: "Mystery of a Disappeared Family."</Title>
            <Data>Client: Mr John Smith
Investigator: Carl Orgen
Case Description: Mr Smith contracted the agency to find his missing family who disappeared without a trace several months ago. 
The assigned investigator must discover all possible leads and find out what happened to them.</Data>
        </TextRecord>
        <TextRecord>
            <Title>#4951: "Election Rival Dossier."</Title>
                <Data>Client: Mr Lucious Halt
Investigator: John Halcyon
Case Description: Mr Halt requested to gather a dossier on his mayor's election competitor Margaret Cumberbatch.
The assigned investigator must find all possible leads and find out everything that might be useful for the client.</Data>
            </TextRecord>
            <TextRecord>
            <Title>#5941: "Kidnapping in the Park."</Title>
            <Data>Client: Mrs Alice Johnson
Investigator: Carl Orgen
Case Description: Mrs Johnson contracted the agency with finding her missing son who was abducted right from the park where he was playing with his friends. 
It is up to the assigned investigator to determine who abducted the boy and where he may be.</Data>
        </TextRecord>
        <TextRecord>
            <Title>#5264: "Mysterious Murder at the Theatre."</Title>
            <Data>Client: Mr Richard Williams.
Investigator: Carl Orgen
Case Description: A mysterious murder has occurred in a theatre and Mr. Williams asks the detective to solve the case and find the culprit. 
The assigned investigator needs to gather evidence, interview witnesses and suspects to find out the circumstances of the crime.</Data>
        </TextRecord>
        <TextRecord>
            <Title>#5367: "Providence Dossier"</Title>
            <Data>Client: Cr4zy_R3I7
Investigator: John Halcyon
Case Description: The agency was contracted to gather information on infamous art-stealer, turned hacker known as Providence, by a renowned software engineer known as Cr4zy_R3I7.
The assigned investigator must investigate all traces of the individual and compile a report for  the client as soon as possible.</Data>
        </TextRecord>
    </DatabaseDaemon>
    <dlink target="pi_irc"/>
    <dlink target="pi_drop"/>
</Computer>