<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="RW_home" name="Riley Whitfield eBook Breeze" type="2" icon="DLCLaptop" allowsDefaultBootModule="true">
    <ports>21,22,443,80</ports>
    <portsForCrack val="3"/>
    <firewall level="4"/>
    <!--misc files-->

    <file path="home/chatlogs" name="irc_log_1041.log">
rilwhitfield: Hey love, I've been thinking about Keira's graduation gift. What do you think about getting her a BMW 5 Series touring?
jordywhitfy: Wow, that's a pretty extravagant gift, Riley. Are you sure it's a good idea? She's just graduating high school, after all.
rilwhitfield: I know it sounds extravagant, but you've seen her grades and how hard she's been working, right? She's earned it.
jordywhitfy: Of course, I'm really proud of her. But, don't you think it's a bit too much for an 18-year-old? I mean, a car like that is expensive to maintain, and I worry it might give her the wrong idea about money.
rilwhitfield: I understand your concerns, but I think it's important to reward her for her dedication to her education. Besides, she'll be heading off to college soon, and having a reliable and safe car will be a huge advantage for her.
jordywhitfy: I get that, but can't we find a more reasonable option? Maybe something that's still safe and reliable but not as pricey. We don't want to spoil her, do we?
rilwhitfield: That's a valid point. I want to encourage her achievements, not spoil her. Maybe we can look into a used BMW 5 Series touring. That way, we can still get her a great car without the same price tag.
jordywhitfy: That could be a good compromise. Let's research some options, check the reviews, and make sure it's within our budget. We want to celebrate her success without going overboard.
rilwhitfield: That sounds fair. We'll find the right balance between rewarding her for her hard work and being responsible parents. Thanks for understanding, Jordyn.
</file>

    <!--!EOS FILE STRUCTURE!-->
    <file path="sys/eSync" name="eSync.exe">#BINARY#</file>
    <file path="sys/eSync" name="config.json">{
	"eOS-auth-api": {
		"device-imei": 353759084570542,
		"client-uuid": "cc0584f4-6d20-11ee-b962-0242ac120002",
		"protocol": "udp",
		"host": "whaddaphone.eoverify.com",
		"port": 3659,
		"max-devices": 1
	},
	"credential-provider":{
        "device-type": "ePhone9s"
		"device-username":"rilwhitfield",
		"obf-password":"YWxwaW5l",
		"pass-default":true
	}
}</file>
    <file path="sys/eSync" name="eSync_connections.log">#BINARY#</file>

<eosDevice name="Riley Whitfield's ePhone 9S" id="rw_eos" icon="ePhone2" empty="false">
    <note>Work to-do
- Meeting with the team at 10 AM to discuss the new project requirements.
   - Don't forget to follow up with the client regarding their feedback on the prototype.
   - Review the pull request from James and provide feedback by EOD.
   - Schedule a code review session for the junior developer, Sarah, this week.
   - Update the project timeline and share it with the team tomorrow.
</note>

<note>to-dos
   - Buy groceries on the way home, and don't forget to pick up milk and eggs.
   - Call Mom to wish her a happy birthday this evening.
   - Set a reminder to go to the gym at 6:30 PM for a workout session.
   - Make a list of weekend activities and plan a hiking trip for Saturday.
   - Check the car's oil and tire pressure this weekend and schedule a service if needed.
</note>
    
    <!-- It's important to keep everything in your files organized - so let's leave some space between tags -->
    
    <mail username="rilwhitfield@entech.com" pass="yP2t73wC"/>
</eosDevice>

</Computer>