<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="playerComp" name="Pretence_Battlestation" type="4" icon="laptop" allowsDefaultBootModule="true">
    <firewall solution="unremitting" additionalTime="0.5"/>
    <ports>21,6881,443,22,25,1433</ports>
    <portsForCrack val="6"/>
    <portRemap>21=3121,80=90,443=821,6881=9171,25=84</portRemap>
    <proxy time="2.8"/>
    
    <!--*Default Applications*-->
    <file path="bin" name="SSHCrack.exe">#SSH_CRACK#</file> <!--SSH - 22-->
    <file path="bin" name="FTPBounce.exe">#FTP_CRACK#</file> <!-- FTP - 21-->
    <file path="bin" name="WebServerWorm.exe">#WEB_CRACK#</file> <!-- WEB - 80-->
    <file path="bin" name="SQLBufferOverflow.exe">#SQL_CRACK#</file> <!--SQL - 1433-->
    <file path="bin" name="eosDeviceScan.exe">#EOS_SCANNER_EXE#</file>
    
    <!--*Personal Diary*-->
    <file path="home/unremittance" name="readme.txt">I guess, if you're reading this, I'm either dead or failsafe didn't work.

No matter the case, congratulations! You've gone to a tremendous amount of effort to find... A lousy diary of some online creep.
If we ever meet in heaven or hell, be sure to find me and tell me was it worth the trouble. Cuz I'm dying to see your confused face.

Anyway, don't touch it. Just leave it as is, it held some meaning to me when I was... Well, alive.</file>

<file path="home/unremittance" name="01.txt">It feels like I'm trapped in this weird dimension under some false pretensions.
I look around and see things that just can't exist under any logical circumstances. Not in a world ruled by the kind to conquer nature.
We've allowed the wealthy to become the lawless, to kill billions in their internal power struggles and, while we all despise it, we keep on acting normal.
How in the hell can we allow it? How can we turn a blind eye to it? There has to be a time when we all take up arms and drag them down from their ivory towers!</file>

<file path="home/unremittance" name="02.txt">
"Centauri", what a stellar name for something so idiotic. I get it, kids want to leave their mark on the world, write their name down in internet history, but I don't quite see a point.
It's not like they have a goal or a cause. They just do gigs left and right hoping someone offers them something big enough, yet I don't quite find it possible. Not how the world works.
Although, I think it's a good place to get myself acquainted with this world, workhorses like this tend to do a lot of work for the bigger and badder. Just what I need right about now.
</file>

<file path="home/unremittance" name="03.txt">
Sunset... The kid seems way too young for this stuff. Too naive, too... brat-ish? I dunno, something about him feels wrong. Looks like C0nst understands it as well.
All his gigs are really harmless, so I don't really mind his presence within our group, but I can't think of actual kids sneaking around the net in our line of work. It just feels wrong.
</file>
<customthemefile path="sys" name="x-server.sys" themePath="Themes/miamithemelightblue.xml"/>
</Computer>