<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="playerComp" name="Pretence_Battlestation" type="4" icon="laptop" allowsDefaultBootModule="true">
    <firewall solution="unremitting" additionalTime="0.5"/>
    <ports>21,6881,443,22,25,1433</ports>
    <portsForCrack val="6"/>
    <portRemap>21=3121,80=90,443=821,6881=9171,25=84</portRemap>
    <proxy time="2.8"/>
    
    <!--*Default Applications*-->
    <file path="bin" name="SSHCrack.exe">#SSH_CRACK#</file> <!--SSH - 22-->
    <file path="bin" name="FTPBounce.exe">#FTP_CRACK#</file> <!-- FTP - 21-->
    <file path="bin" name="WebServerWorm.exe">#WEB_CRACK#</file> <!-- WEB - 80-->
    <file path="bin" name="SQLBufferOverflow.exe">#SQL_CRACK#</file> <!--SQL - 1433-->
    <file path="bin" name="eosDeviceScan.exe">#EOS_SCANNER_EXE#</file>
    
    <!--*Personal Diary*-->
    <file path="home/unremittance" name="readme.txt">I guess, if you're reading this, I'm either dead or failsafe didn't work.

No matter the case, congratulations! You've gone to a tremendous amount of effort to find... A lousy diary of some online creep.
If we ever meet in heaven or hell, be sure to find me and tell me was it worth the trouble. Cuz I'm dying to see your confused face.

Anyway, don't touch it. Just leave it as is, it held some meaning to me when I was... Well, alive.</file>

<file path="home/unremittance" name="01.txt">It feels like I'm trapped in this weird dimension under some false pretensions.
I look around and see things that just can't exist under any logical circumstances. Not in a world ruled by the kind to conquer nature.
We've allowed the wealthy to become the lawless, to kill billions in their internal power struggles and while we all despise it, we keep on acting normal.
How in the hell can we allow it? How can we turn a blind eye to it? There has to be a time when we all take up arms and drag them down from their ivory towers!</file>

<file path="home/unremmitance" name="02.txt">I'm not the only one who's not feeling it's all wrong. It feels better to know it.

These Nightwave people, they do hold the right ideas, but I don't feel like they understand their actions. All these words about doing the right thing... Too metaphorical.
And their approach? They don't take it seriously at all. Whilst their arch nemesis is set out on a mission and is taking thorough steps in it's direction.

This is a recipe for disaster, but at least, these idiots do something good, so I might just stick around until a better team pops up</file>

<file path="home/unremmitance" name="03.txt">Strife... It's surprising to see him join our clusterfuck of a team.

Although, there's not many other people reckless enough to shit on Jintech's doorstep and knock on the door. I mean that's why *I* am here.
He's definitely different. More serious, more ruthless. He definitely has his own beef with Jintech, luckily it won't cause collateral damage.

There is some degree of concern I have though. His record is too clean. No-one knows who he is or where he came from. I should look deeper into this once I have the time.</file>

<file path="home/unremmitance" name="04.txt">I guess, we've got a win. Strife is now our "leader", although Constellation is still pissed about becoming an HR, I feel like it's a good change.

Me and him tend to share a lot of targets and goals, now we can start pushing the others in right direction. I hope to see it all proper soon.</file>
</Computer>