<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="EnWS02" name="EnTech Workstation _09" type="3" ip="156.151.0.92">
  <!--*Amelia Anderson Workstation*-->
  <firewall level="1" additionalTime="1.5"/>
  <ports>80, 22, 1433, 25, 21</ports>
  <portsForCrack val="4" />
  <file path="home/personal" name="irc_autolog_0189">
AmAnders: Hey Crio, I've been thinking about adding some art to my home. Do you have any Manet or Matisse pieces available?

Crio: Hey Amelia, great to hear from you! Manet and Matisse, huh? That's some high-end taste you got there. I do have connections, but they might be a bit out of your budget range.

AmAnders: I figured as much, but it never hurts to ask, right? What do you have in a more affordable range then?

Crio: Well, you know me, always got something up my sleeve. How about a Monet? I've got a beautiful one that you could have on the cheap. It's a fantastic piece, and I can get it for you at a reasonable price.

AmAnders: A Monet, you say? That sounds intriguing. Can you tell me more about it? What's the painting, and how much are we talking?

Crio: It's a Monet water lilies piece, one of his classics. The colors are mesmerizing, and it's a great addition to any space. As for the price, I can let it go for $2,000. It's a steal, trust me.

AmAnders: $2,000 for a Monet? That's quite a deal. I'd love to see some pictures and get more details, but this could be exactly what I'm looking for.

Crio: I thought you'd like that! I'll send you some images of the painting, and you can have a closer look. It's in great condition, and I'm sure you'll love it. Let me know if you're interested, and we can discuss the details further.

AmAnders: Sounds good, Providence! I can't wait to see the pictures. Let's definitely talk more about this Monet. Thanks for offering me this opportunity, and I appreciate your help.

Crio: No problem at all, Amelia. I'm here to make your art dreams come true. I'll send over those pictures shortly, and we can take it from there. Talk to you soon!
</file>
  <positionNear target="EnTechWSCore" position="4" total="12" />
  

</Computer>